Contact

meetrashu09@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/rashika-gupta-aa7a83153 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Human Resources
Management
Customer Service

Rashika Gupta

Sr. Recruiter -HRD at EduGorilla Community Pvt. Ltd. (Aggressively Hiring in multiple profiles please check my post)

Lucknow

Summary

Experienced Recruiter with a demonstrated history of working in the education management industry. Skilled in Microsoft Excel, Customer Service, Microsoft Word, Recruiting, and Public Speaking. Strong human resources professional with a Master's degree focused in Business Administration and Management, General from Maharishi University of Management.

Experience

EduGorilla Community
HR Recruiter
November 2018 - Present (1 year 10 months)
Lucknow Area, India

ARROWAI TECHNOSOFT LLP

H.R Excutive October 2017 - June 2018 (9 months)

Infoseek Software Systems (Brand of My5 Technologies Pvt. Ltd.)
Junior Executive Human Resources
February 2016 - September 2016 (8 months)

Chandganj garden kapoorthala lucknow (U.P)

Sarthak Education Pvt.Ltd.
Counselor
April 2015 - January 2016 (10 months)
Jankipuram sec-G Lucknow(U.P)

SPREADING WINGS RESOURCES (P) LTD.
Back Office Executive
May 2014 - February 2015 (10 months)
Sahara bhawan kapoorthal Lucknow(U.P)

Education

Maharishi University of Management

Master's degree, Business Administration and Management,

General · (2016 - 2017)

Ramabai PG College

Bachelor of Commerce - BCom, Human Resources Management/Personnel Administration, General · (2013 - 2015)